?Shri Ekadasha Rudra Puja. Faggeto Lario, Como (Italy), 16 September 1984.
[ Shree Ekadash Rudra Puja。 1984年9月16日在意大利科莫的Fagato Lario。]
Today, we are doing a special type of puja which is performed in the glory of Ekadasha Rudra.
[ 今天，我们正在做一种特殊的敬拜，这是在第十一届Rudra的荣耀中进行的。]
Rudra is the destructive power of Shiva, of the Spirit.
[ Rudra是湿婆灵魂的毁灭力量。]
[ 湿婆神的毁灭性力量是鲁德拉灵魂的毁灭。]
Now one power, which is His nature, is forgiveness.
[ 现在，一种力量，即其本质，就是宽恕。]
He forgives, because we are human beings, we commit mistakes,
[ 他原谅，因为我们是人类，所以我们会犯错误，]
we do wrong things, we get tempted,
[ 我们做错事，受到诱惑，]
our attention is disturbed – so he forgives us.
[ 他分散了我们的注意力-这就是为什么他原谅我们。]
He also forgives us when we spoil our chastity, we do immoral things,
[ 即使我们破坏我们的圣洁并不道德地行事，他们也会原谅我们，]
we do thieving, and we do things that are against God, talk against Him.
[ 我们偷盗并与上帝作斗争，对他们说话。]
He also forgives our superficialities, jealousies, our lust, our anger.
[ 他还宽恕了我们的肤浅，嫉妒，欲望和愤怒。]
Also He forgives our attachments, petty jealousies, vanities and also possessiveness.
[ 除此之外，他还宽恕了我们的依恋，小嫉妒，骄傲和归属感。]
He forgives our egoistical behaviour and also our subordination to wrong things.
[ 他也原谅我们的利己行为和对错误事物的服从。]
But every action has a reaction, and when He forgives,
[ 但是每一个动作都会有反应，当它原谅时，]
He thinks that He has given you a big grace-mark,
[ 他认为他给了你很大的恩典，]
and that reaction builds up within Him as a wrath,
[ 这种反应以愤怒的形式出现在他们身上，]
against those who are forgiven,[who] try to do greater mistakes.
[ 那些原谅他们的人，试图犯越来越多的错误。]
Specially, after realisation,
[ 特别是在“同化”之后，]
because such a big blessing there is of the realisation –  you’ve got the light and, in the light,
[ 因为在实现自我的巨大祝福之后，您有了光明和光明，]
if you are holding onto a snake then His wrath goes up because he sees how stupid you have been.
[ 如果您拿着蛇，他的愤怒会增加，因为他看到您有多愚蠢。]
(Italian translator is confused so Mother re-iterates)
[ （意大利翻译感到困惑，所以母亲又重生了两次）]
What I am saying is that after realisation, specially,
[ 我是说自满之后，]
He is much more sensitive that,
[ 他非常敏感，]
people who are forgiven and have been given such a big thing like Self-realisation,
[ 被宽恕并接受诸如面试等重大事情的人，]
still they do wrong things then he is much more wrathful.
[ 但是，如果他们做错了事，他们会很生气。]
So, in the balance, the forgiveness starts reducing and the wrathfulness starts increasing.
[ 因此，在平衡中，宽恕开始减少，愤怒开始增加。]
But when He forgives and, as a result of that forgiveness you feel the gratitude,
[ 但是当他原谅了他之后，你会感到感激，]
then His blessings start flowing towards you.
[ 然后他的祝福开始涌向你。]
He gives you tremendous capacity to forgive others.
[ 他为您提供了宽容他人的强大能力。]
He pacifies your anger, He pacifies your lust, He pacifies your greed.
[ 他平息你的愤怒，平息你的欲望，平息你的贪婪。]
Like beautiful dew drop His blessings come on our being and we become really beautiful flowers,
[ 就像美丽的露珠，他的祝福来到了我们的存在，我们成为了真正美丽的花朵，]
and we start shining in the sunshine of His blessings.
[ 我们开始在他的祝福的阳光下闪耀。]
Now He uses His wrath or His destructive power to destroy all that tries to trouble us.
[ 现在，他以他的愤怒或破坏性力量摧毁了那些困扰我们的人。]
He protects realised souls at every point, in every way.
[ 他们以各种方式在各处保持“自我实现”。]
Negative forces try to attack a sahaja yogi but they are all neutralised by His tremendous power of protection.
[ 负势力试图攻击S哈嘉瑜伽士，但由于他的保护所造成的巨大影响，它们被中和了。]
Through his vibratory awareness we are guided into right path.
[ 通过他的有意识的力量，我们被引导向正确的道路。]
All the beautiful blessings of His are described in the Psalm 23 isn’t it, that’s the 23 Psalm ……
[ 在Bhajan（Psalm）23中描述了他所有美丽的描述，Hanna，这是Psalm 23（Psalm）……]
The Lord is my Shepherd” Is all described how he looks after you as a shepherd.
[ 上帝是我的牧者“有种种说法，他照顾你是牧者。]
But He does not look after the evil people He destroys them.
[ 但是他们不照顾坏人，而是消灭他们。]
Those who enter into Sahaja Yoga [and] are still carrying on with their evil nature are destroyed.
[ 那些进入S哈嘉瑜伽并仍然坚持其邪恶本性的人被摧毁了。]
Those who come to Sahaja Yoga and do not meditate and do not rise He destroys,
[ 那些来S哈嘉瑜伽而不冥想，不自我提升的人会摧毁他们，]
or they are thrown out of Sahaja Yoga.
[ 否则他们会被S哈嘉瑜伽抛弃。]
Those who murmur against God and live in a way that is not behoving a sahaja yogi,
[ 谁对上帝发牢骚，过着不适合简单瑜伽士的生活方式，]
He removes them from [it].
[ 他[驱逐]他们。]
So by one force, He protects, by another force, He throws away.
[ 因此，用一种力量，他保护，用另一种力量，他扔掉。]
But His destructive forces when they are built up too much,
[ 但是当它们建造得太多时，它们的破坏力，]
then we call it – now the Ekadasha Rudra is active.
[ 然后我们称之为-第十一届Rudra已启用。]
Now, this Ekadasha Rudra will be expressed when the Kalki itself will start acting,
[ 现在，当Kalki独自开始工作时，将表达第11个Rudra，]
means the destructive power which will destroy all that is negative on this earth and save all that is positive.
[ 意味着破坏力将摧毁地球上所有的消极情绪，并将拯救任何积极的东西。]
So it is very necessary for sahaja yogis to expedite their ascent,
[ 因此，S哈嘉瑜伽士加速崛起非常重要，]
not to be satisfied with the social life or married life or
[ 您是否对社交生活或已婚生活感到满意]
with all the blessings that God has bestowed upon you.
[ 上帝赐予你所有的祝福。]
We always see, what God has done for us, how He has been miraculous to us,
[ 我们总是看到，上帝为我们做了什么，他对我们有多么神奇，]
but we have to see what we have done to ourselves,
[ 但是我们必须看看我们自己做了什么，]
what are we doing about our own ascent and growth.
[ 我们正在为自己的成长和发展做些什么。]
Now the…out of the eleven centres…… Ekadasha, means eleven,
[ 现在…在11个中心中…11表示11，]
the five come from the right side of your void, and five from the left side of your void.
[ 五个来自巴瓦萨加尔的右侧，五个来自巴哈瓦加尔的左侧。]
The first five on the left hand side come from:
[ 出现以下情况时，左前五个保持不变：]
if you have bowed yourself to wrong gurus, or if you have read wrong books,
[ 如果您屈服于错误的老师，或者阅读错误的书籍，]
or if you have been in the company of wrong people,
[ 或者如果您与错误的人在一起，]
or if you have been sympathetic towards people who have been following wrong paths,
[ 或者，如果您对走错路的人表示同情，]
or you have been yourself one of the agents or guru of these wrong people.
[ 否则您自己就是这些错误人士的代理或专家之一。]
Now these five problems can be solved, if we completely give up whatever wrong we have been doing.
[ 现在可以解决这五个问题，如果我们现在做错了什么，请完全解决。]
As Mohammed Sahib has said that you have to beat the Shaitan, means the Satan, with shoes;
[ 正如穆罕默德所说，你必须用鞋子杀死魔鬼。]
but that has to be done not mechanically but from your heart.
[ 但这不是机械地完成的，而是从内心做起的。]
Like many people who come to Sahaja Yoga will tell me,
[ 就像许多来S哈嘉瑜伽的人对我说：]
“My father is following this guru; that father is following that guru,”
[ “我父亲跟随这位大师。那个父亲跟着那个大师，]
and get involved with their father, mother, sister, this,
[ 通过和他的父亲，母亲，姐妹等交往，]
that and try to take them out from those gurus, also get entangled.
[ 并试图使他们脱离那些大师，他们自己也被纠缠。]
Or some of them yield to others’ forces.
[ 或其中一些获得其他权力。]
Like I know of Maureen, who was with me,
[ 我知道和我在一起的莫琳]
and her parents and parents-in-law said that the child must be baptised,
[ 她的父母和亲家说孩子应该受洗，]
and I told her, you cannot get this child baptised because it’s a realised soul.
[ 我对她说，你不能为这个孩子施洗，因为它是一个自我实现的灵魂。]
But she could not, that way, stand up to that,
[ 但是她不能这样]
and she took the child for baptism and the child became very funny – it was really like a mad child.
[ 她带着孩子接受洗礼，孩子变得非常离奇-他真的变得像个疯子。]
Now then she gave up all that and so she has saved.
[ 现在，当她放弃所有这些时，她得以幸免。]
But supposing she had another child and she would have done the same thing,
[ 但是如果他们生了第二个孩子，她也会对他做同样的事情，]
the second child would have been something very, very bad.
[ 因此，另一个孩子的状况会非常糟糕。]
Now, the trouble with sahaja yogis is that anybody who comes to Sahaja Yoga programme thinks he is a sahaja yogi – is not so.
[ 现在，S哈嘉瑜伽士的麻烦在于，凡是参加ah哈嘉瑜伽课程的人都认为自己是a哈嘉瑜伽士-事实并非如此。]
Either you should have very strong sensitivity, or you should feel it in your body,
[ 您必须具有非常强的敏感性，或者您应该在体内感觉到它，]
or with your intelligence you should understand what is Sahaja Yoga.
[ 或者，以您的才智，您应该了解什么是S哈嘉瑜伽。]
A person who is still negative always gets attracted towards another one who is a very,
[ 一个仍然消极的人总是被他吸引，他非常，]
very powerfully negative and does not understand that the other person is so powerfully negative, but gets impressed.
[ 负面因素太多，他不了解自己所影响的人是非常负面的人。]
Under such circumstances, such a person is hit by that negative person and Shiva cannot protect.
[ 在这种情况下，这样的人会成为那个消极人的猎物，而湿婆无法保护她。]
One should not have sympathy with anyone who is negative, whether he is mad,
[ 我们不应该同情那些消极的人，无论他们是疯狂的。]
whether there is something wrong with him, whether he is your relation, or anything.
[ 他是否出了问题，他是你的亲戚，还是其他。]
No sympathy of any kind, on the contrary a kind of a anger should be there for that person,
[ 不应有任何同情，相反，应该对那个人有一种愤怒，]
a kind of a detachment, angry detachment.
[ 一种孤立，胃灼热。]
And this angry detachment is the only time when you have to be angry.
[ 而这种愤怒的分离是您唯一必须生气的时候。]
But I have seen people who have anger for very good sahaja yogis
[ 但是我看到有人对非常好的ah哈嘉瑜伽士感到愤怒]
but not for their own husbands or wives who are extremely negative.
[ 但不是对自己的配偶谁是极端否定的。]
So when the Ekadasha Rudra starts acting on these five sides on the, we should say,
[ 因此，当第十一届Rudra开始在这五个方面开展工作时，我们应该说，]
on the right side it moves, because it comes from the left and moves to the right side,
[ 它们向右移动，因为它们来自左侧并向右移动，]
then a person starts becoming also negative but acting with his ego.
[ 然后，一个人在与自我合作时也会变得消极。]
Such a person may take up a situation into hands and say that
[ 这样的人可以掌握情况，说]
“I am such and such sahaja yogi and I am so, we should do like this and we should behave like this”,
[ “我是如此简单的瑜伽士，我就是这样，我们应该这样做，并且我们应该这样行事”]
and start dictating people. [They] can do anything.
[ 并开始订购人员。 [他]可以做任何事。]
And some mediocres or some half-baked sahaja yogis may try to understand [him],
[ 一些平庸或半成熟的S哈嘉瑜伽士可能会试图理解[他]。]
but most of them will know that, “This fellow is going out, now he’s on his way out!”
[ 但是大多数人都知道：“他要出去了，现在他正要崩溃！”]
So, all these things lead to this left side development, or we can call it on the head,
[ 因此，所有这些东西都在左侧发展，或者我们可以说在头上，]
on the right hand side of your medha, this plate, brain-plate is called as medha in Sanskrit language.
[ 脑板在梵语右侧被称为梵语的Medha，在此语言板上。]
Now, the right sided one, comes from the idea people have that, “I am myself a big guru.”
[ 现在，右侧来自人们的想法，即``我自己是一位伟大的大师''。]
They start preaching about Sahaja Yoga also, as if they have become great gurus.
[ 他们开始宣讲S哈嘉瑜伽，就好像他们已经成为伟大的大师一样。]
We have known some people who give big lectures in any programme
[ 我们知道有些人会在任何程序中进行大型演讲]
and never allow my tape to be played or anything.
[ 也不要让我的磁带随时随地播放。]
They think they have now become experts.
[ 他们感到自己已经成为专家。]
Then some of them say that now we have become so great that we need not do any footsoaking or anything,
[ 然后有些人说，现在我们已经变得如此强大，以至于我们不必做任何水上运动或任何其他事情，]
there’s no need to do meditation –  there are some like that also.
[ 不需要打坐-有一些。]
And then there are some who say that sin can never touch us,
[ 然后有人说罪恶永远无法触及我们，]
now we are sahaja yogis, we are very great evolved souls.
[ 我们现在是S哈嘉瑜伽士，我们是非常伟大的发达灵魂。]
But the worst of all are those who just take my name saying that
[ 但最糟糕的是那些说我名字的人]
“Mother has said so and I am telling you because Mother has said” –
[ “妈妈这么说，我告诉你是因为妈妈说了”-]
when I have never said such a thing, is all falsehood.
[ 虽然我从未说过，但这全是谎言。]
Now there are some people who use Sahaja Yoga money and exploit Sahaja Yoga in such a way,
[ 现在有些人用S哈嘉瑜伽的钱来破坏S哈嘉瑜伽，]
exploit them, sahaja yogis also sometimes.
[ 利用它们，有时甚至利用S哈嘉瑜伽士。]
And such people become very inauspicious.
[ 这样的人变得非常不吉利。]
Anyone who tries such things will go out of Sahaja Yoga with disgrace.
[ 任何尝试这样的人都会不尊重地走出S哈嘉瑜伽。]
But one should never go near such a person,
[ 但是永远不要去这样的人，]
have nothing to do with such a person, have no sympathies.
[ 不应有同情心，对这样的人没有同情心。]
Because this inauspiciousness will hurt anyone to any extent, so better keep out of such people.
[ 因为这些不幸的人可以在任何程度上伤害任何人，所以最好远离这些人。]
When these ten Ekadashas are developed within a person,
[ 当这十一个人在一个人中发展时，]
then definitely such a person gets diseases like cancer and incurable horrible diseases.
[ 因此，这样的人肯定会患上许多疾病，例如癌症和无法治愈的可怕疾病。]
Specially, when the eleventh one which is actually here,
[ 特别是当真正在这里的贾瓦·鲁德拉（Gyarva Rudra）]
which is the Virata’s chakra, which is the collectivity –
[ 这是维拉特的圈子，是集体-]
when it is affected as well, then such a person cannot get out of this disease.
[ 当它也受到影响时，那么这样的人就无法摆脱这种疾病。]
But these…out of these even five are combined, supposing, with Mooladhara or with Agnya,
[ 但是即使是这些……如果其中有五个假设与基础或命令结合在一起，]
then they get into very serious type of dirty diseases.
[ 然后，他们会接触到非常严重的肮脏疾病。]
That’s why, I always say that be careful about your Agnya chakra,
[ 这就是为什么我总是说要注意您的命令周期，]
because that is one of the worst things, that, once it starts getting combined with these Ekadashas,
[ 因为这是最坏的情况，所以当这个XI开始与XI结合时，]
part of the Ekadashas, then anything can happen to a person,
[ 所以任何事情都会发生在一个人身上，]
he can meet with a horrible accident, he can suddenly be hit by someone, could be murdered by someone,
[ 他可能会发生一场可怕的事故，有人可以突然杀死他，有人可以杀死他，]
anything can happen to such a person who has got the right Agnya and also any one of the Ekadashas, right or left.
[ 拥有命令权的人和演奏十一，右或左的人都可能发生任何事情。]
That means, the five of these, if they, any one of the five,
[ 也就是说，如果有五个，如果有五个，]
if they combine with Agnya Chakra, the protective powers of God are minimum.
[ 如果将它们与顺服相结合，上帝的保护能力将变得微不足道。]
So, to keep your Agnya chakra alright, say now I am speaking, now you should watch Me constantly,
[ 因此，为了保持您的命令周期正确，现在我在讲话，您应该经常看着我，]
so that there is thoughtless awareness and the Agnya chakra is soothed out.
[ 这样就可以不间断地使命令周期平静。]
But, don’t pay attention here and there all the time.
[ 但是，不要一直在这里和那里。]
Then you will find that, gradually, your attention will neutralise into thoughtless awareness,
[ 然后，您会发现，慢慢地，您的思想变得沉思了，]
and your attention would be fixed in such a manner that you don’t have to worry about anything.
[ 这样您的心灵就会得到治愈，您将不必担心任何事情。]
In thoughtless awareness nobody can touch you, that’s your fortress.
[ 尼尔维查里塔没有人可以触摸你，这是你的堡垒。]
By meditation, one must establish thoughtless awareness, that is the sign that you are rising higher.
[ 通过冥想，您应该在nirvicharita中建立，这表明您正在高涨。]
Many people do meditation and say, “Alright, Mother we are doing.”
[ 许多人打坐说：“好吧，妈妈，我们正在做。”]
Mechanically, they do and say, “I did this, I did this, and I did this!”
[ 他们机械地说，“我做到了，我做到了，然后我做到了！”]
But did you achieve your thoughtless awareness, minimum of minimum?
[ 但是，至少您实现了流畅的思维？]
Have you felt your cool breeze coming out of your head?
[ 您是否感到头顶冒出冷气？]
Otherwise, if you are doing something mechanically, it is not going to help; help you or help anyone.
[ 否则，如果您正在机械地做某事，那将无济于事。既无济于事，也无济于事。]
So, after realisation, as you are very well protected,
[ 因此，自我实现之后，由于您受到了很好的保护，]
you have all the blessings and a great future,
[ 您有所有的祝福和美好的未来，]
you also have a great possibility of a  complete annihilation.
[ 您也很有可能被完全摧毁。]
I would say, to give an analogy, you are climbing, and everybody is supporting you to climb,
[ 打个比方，我想说的是，您正在攀登，每个人都在帮助您攀登，]
holding your hand, and there are so many things by which you are protected,
[ 手牵着手，有很多东西受到保护，]
to be taken upward, there’s no possibility of falling off by mistake also,
[ 不可能意外跌倒在你身上，]
but if you try to remove your bondages with Truth and Love and
[ 但是，如果您尝试消除与真相和爱的联系，]
all the time try to hit the people who are trying to support you,
[ 一直试图杀死支持你的人，]
then you fall from a great height, greater height.
[ 然后，您从高处坠落，从高处坠落。]
I mean, the greater height you rise, the greater you fall, and with a greater force also, much more deeper.
[ 我的意思是，您升高的高度越高，下降的次数就越多，并且用力越大，深度就越深。]
But every effort is made by the Divine, every support is given to you, every care is taken – despite that,
[ 但是，上帝尽了一切努力，给予了您一切支持，也给予了一切照顾-尽管如此，]
if you want to fall, then from that height, is very dangerous.
[ 如果要从那个高度跌落，那是非常危险的。]
But Ekadasha Rudra, at that time, at such a time when somebody tries to harm the cause of Sahaja Yoga,
[ 但是第十一世Rudra当一个人试图损害S哈嘉瑜伽的存在时，]
after being in Sahaja Yoga, then hits you so badly that the whole attack is very widespread.
[ 尽管处于S哈嘉瑜伽运动中，但它仍然使您丧命，以至于整个袭击非常普遍。]
But the whole family can be protected if there are few people of that family doing Sahaja Yoga work; could be protected.
[ 但是，如果该家庭中只有少数人从事S哈嘉瑜伽的工作，那么整个家庭都将受到保护。可以被保护。]
But in case the family that is against all the time of sahaja yogis and try to trouble them,
[ 但是，如果有家人一直反对against哈嘉瑜伽士，并试图骚扰他们，]
can be completely destroyed, in a very bad way.
[ 它们以非常糟糕的方式被完全摧毁。]
Now these Ekadasha Rudras come out of, as I told you, from the Void.
[ 正如我告诉您的那样，现在这十一只Rudras从Bhavsagar出来。]
So, we can say that the destruction part of it comes from the Void mainly.
[ 因此，我们可以说其破坏的一部分主要来自Bhavsagar。]
But these are the powers, all are given in one person that is the Mahavishnu, that is Lord Jesus Christ.
[ 但是这些都是权力，都是由一个大人，即大主耶稣基督赋予的。]
Because He’s the support of the whole Universe,
[ 因为它是整个宇宙的基础，]
He’s the personification of Omkara, he’s the Personification of vibrations.
[ 它是Omkar的形式，它是意识的形式。]
So when He gets angry then the whole Universe starts breaking.
[ 因此，当他生气时，整个宇宙开始灭亡。]
As He personifies the power of the Mother which is penetrating into every atom,
[ 就像在母亲的力量中一样，在原子中，]
into every molecule, and to every human being, into every [thing] that is living and non-living:
[ 在每个分子和每个人中形成的形态，弥漫着一切鲜活和无生命的事物：]
once it gets disturbed the whole thing gets into a jeopardy.
[ 一旦他们变得躁动不安，整个事情就会陷入麻烦。]
So the pleasing of Christ is very important.
[ 因此，基督的幸福非常重要。]
Now Christ has said, “You have to be like small children”
[ 现在耶稣说：“你必须像小孩子一样”]
That is, the innocence, the purity of the heart is the best way you can please Him.
[ ...这是无知，内心的纯洁是使他们快乐的最好方法。]
As in the West, specially, people have developed their brains too much,
[ 尤其是在西方人，他们已经发展了很多思想，]
they try to play about with words and think that nobody knows what they are doing.
[ 他们尝试玩文字游戏，以为没人知道自己在做什么。]
All such people must know that everything you do is known to God.
[ 所有这些人都应该知道，无论您做什么，上帝都知道。]
If you are not clean in the heart, it is very dangerous for anybody to pose as if he’s a very good sahaja yogi.
[ 如果您内心不清晰，表明您是一位非常好的天然瑜伽士是非常危险的。]
Such people are not possessed, nor they are conditioned, nor they are egoistical,
[ 这样的人不受阻碍，既不保守也不自负，]
but they are very cunning clever people and they are quite aware, as to what they are doing.
[ 但是他们是非常聪明的人，他们非常了解自己在做什么。]
But, there are people who get possessed also and then they, in that ,
[ 但是，有些人被打扰了，然后，]
they try to destroy themselves or cry and weep and do all kinds of things.
[ 他们试图破坏自己或洗手，做各种各样的事情。]
There are some who think that if they hurt themselves
[ 有些人认为如果他们伤害了自己]
or do some sort of an extreme thing then God will be happy -are sadly mistaken.
[ 或者，如果您进行某种极端的工作，那么上帝会很高兴-完全错误。]
If you cannot enjoy in Sahaja Yoga, then you should know that something is wrong with you.
[ 如果您无法享受S哈嘉瑜伽，那您应该知道自己有毛病。]
If you cannot feel happy in Sahaja Yoga then you must know that there’s something definitely wrong with you.
[ 如果您无法在S哈嘉瑜伽中感到幸福，那么您应该知道自己确实有问题。]
If you cannot enjoy the company of sahaja yogis, then be sure something is wrong with you.
[ 如果您无法享受S哈嘉瑜伽士的陪伴，请确保您有什么毛病。]
If you cannot laugh and appreciate the greatness of God, then there’s something wrong with you.
[ 如果你不能笑并欣赏上帝的伟大，那你就出了点问题。]
If you are still worried about negative people and their problems then know that there’s something wrong with you.
[ 如果您仍然担心负面的人和他们的问题，请知道您有问题。]
If you have sympathies with negative people, then also there’s something wrong with you.
[ 如果您对消极的人有同情，那么您就有毛病了。]
But if you have anger for negative and all that is negative that is against Sahaja Yoga, then you are there.
[ 但是，如果您对the哈嘉瑜伽有负面和所有负面情绪，那么您就在那里。]
When this thing gets matured then you become the power of Ekadasha Rudra yourself.
[ 当这件事成熟时，您自己将成为第十一届Rudra的力量。]
Anybody who will try to insult you or to do any harm, will collapse.
[ 任何试图侮辱您或对您造成伤害的人都会崩溃。]
It has happened with many people who tried to be insulting to me or tried to harm me or anyway….
[ 这发生在许多试图侮辱我或试图伤害我或以任何方式伤害我的人身上。]
sometimes I am quite worried about them.
[ 有时候我很担心他们。]
So one has to be in such a way that they become the Ekadasha.
[ 因此，您必须以成为XI的方式。]
Nobody can touch such people.
[ 没有人可以碰到这样的人。]
But such a person is full of compassion and forgiveness.
[ 但是这样的人充满了怜悯和宽恕。]
As a result, Ekadasha acts much faster.
[ 结果，XI的工作速度非常快。]
The more compassionate you are the more powerful Ekadasha becomes.
[ 您越富有同情心，XI就会变得越强大。]
The more collective you become, the more Ekadasha acts.
[ 集体越多，XI的实现就越多。]
Many people have a habit of receding back into their exclusion and saying
[ 许多人有退缩的习惯，说]
“Oh we better be at home and it’s alright,” but they don’t know what they are missing.
[ “哦，我们在家感觉更好，那很好，”但是他们不知道要离开什么。]
Whatever may be your experience with others, you should stick-on together, always attend programmes,
[ 无论您与他人的经历如何，您都应该团结在一起，始终参与计划，]
take leadership, go ahead with it, work it out and you will be blessed thousand- fold.
[ 带领，继续下去，完成它，你就会被祝福一千遍。]
Ekadasha Rudra are all the powers, I would say, of destruction, together.
[ 我想说，第十一届Rudra拥有毁灭的全部力量。]
Is the power, destructive power of Shri Ganesha.
[ 这就是Shri Ganesh的破坏力。]
It is the destructive power of Brahma, Vishnu, Mahesha.
[ 这是梵天，毗湿奴和马哈希的破坏力。]
It is the destructive power of the Mother.
[ 这是母亲的破坏力。]
Is the destructive power of the Ganesha…and four of these are Bhairava and Hanumana, Kartikeya and Ganesha.
[ 这些是甘尼萨（Ganesha）的破坏力……其中有四名是Bhairava和Hanuman，Karthikeya和Ganesha。]
Also the powers of Sadashiva and of the Adishakti.
[ 沙克提（Saksti）也拥有“萨达斯瓦（Sadasiva）”和阿迪（Adi）的力量。]
All the destructive powers of all the incarnations are Ekadashas.
[ 所有化身的破坏力都是第十一位。]
Now the last but not the least, is the destructive power of Hiranyagarbha which is the Collective Brahmadeva.
[ 不再是最终的perkam，而是“婆罗门”集体的“ Hiranyagarbha”的破坏力。]
And this power when it acts, every atom explodes, the whole atomic energy goes into a destructive power.
[ 当这种能力发挥作用时，每个原子都会爆炸，整个原子能变成破坏力。]
So, thus, the complete total destructive power is Ekadasha Rudra.
[ 因此，Ekadash Rudra是绝对的破坏力。]
It’s extremely powerful, explosive, but it’s not blind.
[ 它非常强大，爆炸性，但不是盲目的。]
It’s very discriminative and extremely delicately woven.
[ 这是非常明智的，而且编织得很精致。]
It avoids all the good points and attacks the wrong things and it hits at the right time,
[ 它可以保存所有优点，并攻击错误的事物，并在适当的时间发动攻击，]
at the right point, direct, without hitting anything that is good in between.
[ 在正确的位置，笔直，而不会杀死它们之间的任何东西。]
Now the glance of Ekadasha Rudra falls upon someone, say, for example,
[ 例如，现在第11个Rudra转向某人，]
and there is something in between which is divine or which is a positive thing [then] it penetrates through positive,
[ 在中间是神圣的东西或是积极的东西[然后]它越过了积极的东西，]
without harming the positive and hits the negative.
[ 在不损害正面和消极的前提下。]
It cools down somebody and burns another.
[ 它使某人冷却并烧毁另一人。]
Not freezing, it doesn’t freeze, it cools down. (Laughter.)
[ 它不冷，不冻结，它冷却。 （笑声。）]
So that is how it works with such care and such delicacy.
[ 因此，他们以这种谨慎和微妙的方式进行这项工作。]
And it is tremendously sharp also.
[ 而且速度也很快。]
And it’s very painful.
[ 这是非常痛苦的。]
It’s not like cutting the neck in one shot, it goes on slowly, slowly.
[ 它不像一次割脖子（射击），而是缓慢移动。]
All the horrible tortures that you have learnt or heard about are expressions of Ekadasha only.
[ 您所学到或听到的所有可怕的折磨只是XI的表现。]
For example, take the case of cancer.
[ 例如，以癌症为例。]
In the cancer thing, you see, the nose is removed, the tongues are removed,
[ 看到癌症的话，鼻子被移开，舌头被移开，]
then the gullet is removed, then everything goes on, one after [another], being removed with terrible pain, you see.
[ 然后食道死亡，然后一切都这样，一个接一个地移动，痛苦地消除了。]
Take leprosy for example, the lepers cannot feel their fingers,
[ 以麻风病为例，麻风病人无法感觉到手指，]
they cannot feel it, so the…any rat or anything eats their fingers they can’t feel it,
[ 他们感觉不到，这就是原因。。。任何老鼠或任何东西都食指而他们感觉不到，]
so they start losing their fingers, that is how Ekadasha eats up people, devours.
[ 于是他们开始失去手指，像这个十一吃人，吃了他们。]
But this wrathfulness of the Father can be very gentle and could be very sweet, when it comes to His own children.
[ 但是，关于至高无上的父亲，关于他自己的孩子的这种怨恨可能非常温柔和甜蜜。]
The story is about the Mother – once She got very angry, the Primordial Mother.
[ 这个故事是关于母亲的-一旦她非常生气，母亲等。]
And She was so angry, She wanted to destroy the whole world with Her Ekadasha power and
[ 她非常生气，她想通过自己的第十一力量摧毁整个世界，]
She tried to destroy the whole world.
[ 他试图摧毁整个世界。]
When She went into that mood, the Father Himself felt that She is being [a] bit too much angry.
[ 当她升任这个职位时，父亲自己意识到她很生气。]
So when She started destroying, and She was going right and left,
[ 所以当她开始大肆破坏时，她开始左右走动，]
He did not know what to do, so He took Her child, that means representing sahaja yogi, you can say,
[ 他不知道该怎么办，于是他带着孩子，这对to哈嘉瑜伽士来说，可以说，]
representing Christ or representing anyone of these great children of Her’s, that he put the child under Her feet.
[ 基督或他们的这些大孩子，他们将孩子放在他们的脚下。]
So, when She was stamping, suddenly She saw Her own child under Her feet and Her such a big tongue came out.
[ 因此，当她踩着脚走路时，突然她看见自己的孩子在脚下，大舌头出来了。]
She just stopped. Balancing. But this has happened only once. (laughter)
[ 她立刻停了下来。均衡。但这只发生了一次。 （笑声）]
So, after the Ekadasha Rudra, ultimately the complete destruction comes through the anger of Sadashiva.
[ 因此，在Ekadash Rudra之后，彻底的毁灭最终是通过Sadashiva的愤怒而来的。]
When the final total destruction takes place.
[ 当最终的彻底破坏发生时。]
So thus we have seen how Ekadasha Rudra acts and how sahaja yogis have to become themselves Ekadasha Rudra.
[ 因此，通过这种方式，我们了解了第十一届Rudra的工作方式，以及S哈嘉瑜伽士自身如何成为第十一届Rudra。]
Now to develop this power one has to develop a tremendous power of detachment,
[ 现在要发展这种力量，就必须发展巨大的脱离力量，]
power of detachment, detachment from negative.
[ Ana Sakti的力量，来自Negative的Ana Sakti。]
For example, negativity can come from very near people,
[ 例如，消极情绪可能来自非常亲密的人，]
like brother, mother, sister, could come from friends, could come from relatives.
[ 就像兄弟，母亲，姐妹一样，朋友可以来，亲戚可以来。]
It could come from a country, it could come from your political ideas, economic ideas, anything like that.
[ 它可能来自一个国家，也可能来自您的政治观点，经济观点或其他任何观点。]
Any misidentification can destroy your power of Ekadasha Rudra.
[ 任何误解都可能破坏您的第11个Rudra的力量。]
So it is not only sufficient to say that “I am surrendered to Sahaja Yoga and I am a sahaja yogi,”
[ 因此，仅仅说“我致力于S哈嘉瑜伽，而我是S哈嘉瑜伽士”是不够的。]
but you must know mentally also what is Sahaja Yoga.
[ 但是，您也凭智慧知道什么是S哈嘉瑜伽。]
So that, intelligently, you understand what is Sahaja Yoga.
[ 因此，无意识地，您了解什么是S哈嘉瑜伽。]
Because in the West specially people are over-intelligent
[ 因为人们非常聪明，尤其是在西方]
and if the light of Sahaja Yoga does not enter into their intelligence you can never overcome your attachments.
[ 而且，如果S哈嘉瑜伽的光没有进入您的智力，您将永远无法消除自己的感觉。]
That doesn’t mean you talk too much about Sahaja Yoga or you give lectures on that,
[ 这并不意味着您谈论很多关于ah哈嘉瑜伽的话题，也没有为此发表演讲，]
but mentally you should also understand what is Sahaja Yoga.
[ 但是即使有智慧，您也应该了解什么是S哈嘉瑜伽。]
Today is a special day when it has been asked that we should have Ekadasha Rudra puja,
[ 今天是特别的一天，有人要求我们表演Ekadash Rudra Puja，]
and is for all kinds of false religious sects and false gurus and false religions,
[ 这是针对各种错误的宗教教派，错误的宗师和错误的宗教，]
which are followed in the name of God, or any religion that does not say about Self-realisation
[ 奉上帝之名或任何不讲自我实现的宗教追随者]
and does not achieve Self-realisation and does not get connected with God, is false.
[ 并且没有实现自我实现并且没有与上帝联系，是错误的。]
So any such thing that is just faith and talks of God but has no connection with God cannot be a true religion.
[ 因此，任何仅是信仰与上帝之间的对话，而与上帝没有联系的事物，都不是真正的宗教。]
Of course, it gives a balance to people, but in giving that balance,
[ 当然，它可以使人们保持平衡，但是在保持平衡的同时，]
if people live on that money and try to enjoy a wealth out of that money,
[ 如果人们靠那笔钱为生，并尝试享受其中的一种，]
then it is not even at the very lower level is the religion.
[ 那么它甚至还没有达到最低的宗教水平。]
Like a balance, you, see, religion has to give you a balance to begin with, but in that balancing when they tell,
[ 您会发现，就像一种平衡一样，第一宗教会给您带来平衡，但是当他们说到这种平衡时，]
“You have to be balanced, but give me money for that, you must give me money, give me all your purse, give me everything,”
[ “你必须保持平衡，但这要给我钱。你必须给我钱，给我你所有的钱包，给我一切。”]
then that cannot be balanced, it does not even have a slightest thing of the blessings of God.
[ 这样就无法平衡，其中就没有丝毫上帝的祝福。]
Or any religion that makes you bow to anybody else but the incarnation, is no religion.
[ 或者，任何将您屈服于其他人但不屈服于化身的宗教都不是宗教。]
That’s another one which is absolutely false.
[ 这是另一个绝对不正确的事实。]
The real religion will give you a balance and will always talk about the ascent.
[ 真正的宗教会给你一个平衡，并总是谈论超越。]
But they will not ask for money or make one man something great as venerated.
[ 但是他们不会要求金钱或通过使一个人变得伟大而荣誉他。]
Thus, we should learn to discriminate between falsehood, negative things and real things.
[ 因此，我们必须学会区分谎言，负面事物和真实事物。]
Once you develop that discrimination through vibratory awareness,
[ 一旦您以有意识的力量发展了审慎的智力，]
or through your intelligence, you are in the control of yourself.
[ 或者由于您的才智，您可以控制自己。]
And then you become that power of Ekadasha, when you establish your maturity.
[ 然后，当您成熟时，您便成为了第十一个力量。]
Today, I bless you all, that you all become the power of Ekadasha Rudra
[ 今天，我祝福大家，大家都可以成为第十一届Rudra的力量。]
and you develop that sincerity which takes you to that state.
[ 并且您发展出真理，将您带到那个位置。]
May God Bless you.
[ 愿上帝保佑你]